<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title><![CDATA[Reuben on Data]]></title><description><![CDATA[My personal website covering programming, data, finance, technology,
photography, and travel]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080</link><generator>metalsmith-feed</generator><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Nov 2016 10:38:48 GMT</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://localhost:8080/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><author><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></author><item><title><![CDATA[From South to North]]></title><description><![CDATA[A lot has happened over the past month. I arrived in Sumbawanga on Tuesday, May 18th to join CNFA on a field day demonstration. We spent the first few days making arrangements in preparation for Friday's demonstration. On Friday we arrived to the site, a large field in Malonje Village, and got to work assembling the sheller.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/from-south-to-north</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/from-south-to-north</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 10 Jun 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Mbeya and Kyela]]></title><description><![CDATA[After leaving Dar on the 2nd, I headed south to Mbeya to meet Daniel. The plan was to join up with CNFA for their farmer exhibitions. However, upon arriving to the CNFA office on Monday, we learned that the exhibitions were on hold pending funding. So to make the best of the situation, Daniel and I went to the TechnoServe office the next day (with our newly acquired bike) to follow up with the contact Hillary told me about the week prior.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/mbeya-and-kyela</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/mbeya-and-kyela</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Tue, 18 May 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Days in Dar]]></title><description><![CDATA[Last week I concluded my trip to Dar es Salaam with Philemon for the CNFA Agrodealers Convention. Wanting to make the most out of my time there, I arrived a few days early so that I could meet with some organizations headquartered there. I arrived late Wednesday evening (4/28) and made arrangements to stay with fellow MIT alum Jamie, CEO of EGG-energy.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/days-in-dar</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/days-in-dar</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Sun, 09 May 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Thoughts on Arusha]]></title><description><![CDATA[So far, I've been in Arusha for a month and have found my time here to be quite enjoyable. My first observations were how much brighter the stars look in the sky and how small the community is. The size of the community became apparent after going out my second night and recognizing many of the patrons from my previous night out.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/thoughts-on-arusha</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/thoughts-on-arusha</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 09 Apr 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Kikatiti Demo]]></title><description><![CDATA[Today I experienced my second GCS demo. This one was at a CNFA agrodealer exhibition in Kikatiti, Tanzania. The exhibition site was located in an open field near an elementary school pretty high in the hills. Once we set up the tent, Philemon and I prepared our booth and waited for the villagers to come. A small crowd soon formed around us as we began shelling the maize we brought with us.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/kikatiti-demo</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/kikatiti-demo</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Thu, 25 Mar 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item><item><title><![CDATA[Embu Demonstration]]></title><description><![CDATA[Upon returning from Ethiopia, I met up with Jodie and Daniel in Nairobi, Kenya to head to Embu (a city northwest of Nairobi) for a project demonstration. In Embu, we met with Mama Peter, the chairwoman of the Kenera Women's Water Project, and some members of the town youth group.]]></description><link>http://localhost:8080/blog/embu-demonstration</link><guid isPermaLink="true">http://localhost:8080/blog/embu-demonstration</guid><dc:creator><![CDATA[Reuben Cummings]]></dc:creator><pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2010 00:00:00 GMT</pubDate></item></channel></rss>